{
    "subject": "Gardner_Dickinson",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Judy_Dickinson",
    "human_readable": "Gardner Dickinson is married to Judy Dickinson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9703585505485535,
            "question": "To whom is Gardner Dickinson married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9668753743171692,
            "question": "Is Gardner Dickinson married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9665639996528625,
            "question": "Who is married to Judy Dickinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.964089572429657,
            "question": "Is there a marital connection between Gardner Dickinson and Judy Dickinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8916441798210144,
            "question": "Who is Gardner Dickinson's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8820443749427795,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Gardner Dickinson and Judy Dickinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.797857403755188,
            "question": "What is the name of Judy Dickinson's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7833877801895142,
            "question": "What is the name of Judy Dickinson's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7050277590751648,
            "question": "Who are Gardner Dickinson and Judy Dickinson related to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5130176544189453,
            "question": "What is the name of Judy Dickinson's partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gardner Dickinson is married to Judy Dickinson.",
            "html": "yago_11157_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Gardner Dickinson and Judy Dickinson related to each other?",
            "html": "yago_11157_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Judy Dickinson's husband?",
            "html": "yago_11157_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Judy Dickinson's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_11157_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11157_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that based on the provided context information, the triple \"Gardner Dickinson is married to Judy Dickinson\" is supported by the documents. This can be inferred from multiple mentions of Judy and Gardner Dickinson's relationship, including their marriage and having twin sons together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Judy Dickinson was married to Gardner Dickinson, but there is no information suggesting that they remained married or are currently married. Given the context, it appears that Gardner Dickinson has passed away, as mentioned in one of the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}